{
    "name": "Japanese N5 Vocabulary", 
    "vocab": [
        {
            "answer": "あう (to meet)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"会う\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to meet (あう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"会う\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "会う (あう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to meet\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あお (blue)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"青\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "blue (あお)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"青\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "青 (あお)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"blue\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あおい (blue)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"青い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "blue (あおい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"青い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "青い (あおい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"blue\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あか (red)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"赤\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "red (あか)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"赤\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "赤 (あか)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"red\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あかい (red)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"赤い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "red (あかい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"赤い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "赤い (あかい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"red\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あかるい (bright)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"明い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "bright (あかるい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"明い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "明い (あかるい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"bright\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あき (autumn)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"秋\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "autumn (あき)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"秋\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "秋 (あき)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"autumn\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あく (to open, to become open)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"開く\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to open, to become open (あく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"開く\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "開く (あく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to open, to become open\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あける (to open)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"開ける\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to open (あける)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"開ける\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "開ける (あける)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to open\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あげる (to give)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"上げる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to give (あげる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"上げる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "上げる (あげる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to give\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あさ (morning)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"朝\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "morning (あさ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"朝\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "朝 (あさ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"morning\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あさごはん (breakfast)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"朝御飯\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "breakfast (あさごはん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"朝御飯\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "朝御飯 (あさごはん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"breakfast\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "day after tomorrow", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"あさって\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あさって", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"day after tomorrow\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あし (foot, leg)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"足\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "foot, leg (あし)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"足\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "足 (あし)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"foot, leg\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あした (tomorrow)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"明日\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "tomorrow (あした)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"明日\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "明日 (あした)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"tomorrow\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "over there", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"あそこ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あそこ", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"over there\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あそぶ (to play, to make a visit)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"遊ぶ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to play, to make a visit (あそぶ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"遊ぶ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "遊ぶ (あそぶ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to play, to make a visit\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あたたかい (warm)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"暖かい\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "warm (あたたかい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"暖かい\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "暖かい (あたたかい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"warm\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あたま (head)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"頭\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "head (あたま)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"頭\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "頭 (あたま)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"head\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あたらしい (new)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"新しい\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "new (あたらしい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"新しい\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "新しい (あたらしい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"new\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "there", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"あちら\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あちら", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"there\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あつい (hot)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"暑い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "hot (あつい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"暑い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "暑い (あつい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"hot\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あつい (hot to the touch)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"熱い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "hot to the touch (あつい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"熱い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "熱い (あつい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"hot to the touch\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あつい (kind, deep, thick)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"厚い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "kind, deep, thick (あつい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"厚い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "厚い (あつい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"kind, deep, thick\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "over there", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"あっち\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あっち", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"over there\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あと (afterwards)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"後\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "afterwards (あと)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"後\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "後 (あと)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"afterwards\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "you", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"あなた\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あなた", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"you\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あに ((humble) older brother)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"兄\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "(humble) older brother (あに)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"兄\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "兄 (あに)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"(humble) older brother\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あね ((humble) older sister)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"姉\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "(humble) older sister (あね)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"姉\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "姉 (あね)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"(humble) older sister\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "that over there", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"あの\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あの", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"that over there\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "um...", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"あの\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あの", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"um...\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "apartment", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"アパート\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "アパート", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"apartment\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to bathe, to shower", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"あびる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あびる", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to bathe, to shower\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あぶない (dangerous)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"危ない\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "dangerous (あぶない)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"危ない\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "危ない (あぶない)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"dangerous\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あまい (sweet)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"甘い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "sweet (あまい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"甘い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "甘い (あまい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"sweet\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "not very", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"あまり\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あまり", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"not very\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あめ (rain)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"雨\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "rain (あめ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"雨\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "雨 (あめ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"rain\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あめ (candy)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"飴\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "candy (あめ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"飴\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "飴 (あめ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"candy\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あらう (to wash)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"洗う\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to wash (あらう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"洗う\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "洗う (あらう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to wash\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to be, to have (used for inanimate objects)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ある\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ある", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to be, to have (used for inanimate objects)\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あるく (to walk)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"歩く\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to walk (あるく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"歩く\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "歩く (あるく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to walk\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "that", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"あれ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あれ", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"that\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "good", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"いい/よい\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "いい/よい", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"good\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "no", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"いいえ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "いいえ", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"no\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "いう (to say)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"言う\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to say (いう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"言う\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "言う (いう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to say\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "いえ (house)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"家\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "house (いえ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"家\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "家 (いえ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"house\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "how", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"いかが\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "いかが", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"how\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "いく (to go)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"行く\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to go (いく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"行く\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "行く (いく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to go\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "how many?, how old?", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"いくつ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "いくつ", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"how many?, how old?\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "how much?", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"いくら\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "いくら", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"how much?\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "いけ (pond)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"池\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "pond (いけ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"池\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "池 (いけ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"pond\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "いしゃ (medical doctor)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"医者\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "medical doctor (いしゃ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"医者\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "医者 (いしゃ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"medical doctor\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "chair", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"いす\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "いす", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"chair\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "いそがしい (busy, irritated)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"忙しい\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "busy, irritated (いそがしい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"忙しい\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "忙しい (いそがしい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"busy, irritated\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "いたい (painful)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"痛い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "painful (いたい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"痛い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "痛い (いたい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"painful\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "いち (one)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"一\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "one (いち)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"一\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "一 (いち)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"one\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "いちにち ((1) one day, (2) first of month)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"一日\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "(1) one day, (2) first of month (いちにち)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"一日\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "一日 (いちにち)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"(1) one day, (2) first of month\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "best, first", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"いちばん\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "いちばん", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"best, first\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "when", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"いつ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "いつ", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"when\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "いつか (five days, fifth day)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"五日\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "five days, fifth day (いつか)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"五日\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "五日 (いつか)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"five days, fifth day\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "いっしょ (together)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"一緒\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "together (いっしょ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"一緒\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "一緒 (いっしょ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"together\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "いつつ (five)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"五つ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "five (いつつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"五つ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "五つ (いつつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"five\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "always", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"いつも\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "いつも", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"always\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "いぬ (dog)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"犬\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "dog (いぬ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"犬\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "犬 (いぬ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"dog\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "いま (now)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"今\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "now (いま)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"今\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "今 (いま)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"now\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "いみ (meaning)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"意味\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "meaning (いみ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"意味\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "意味 (いみ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"meaning\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "いもうと ((humble) younger sister)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"妹\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "(humble) younger sister (いもうと)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"妹\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "妹 (いもうと)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"(humble) younger sister\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "いや (unpleasant)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"嫌\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "unpleasant (いや)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"嫌\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "嫌 (いや)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"unpleasant\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "いりぐち (entrance)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"入口\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "entrance (いりぐち)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"入口\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "入口 (いりぐち)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"entrance\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "いる (to be, to have (used for people and animals))", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"居る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to be, to have (used for people and animals) (いる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"居る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "居る (いる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to be, to have (used for people and animals)\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "いる (to need)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"要る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to need (いる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"要る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "要る (いる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to need\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "いれる (to put in)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"入れる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to put in (いれる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"入れる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "入れる (いれる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to put in\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "いろ (colour)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"色\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "colour (いろ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"色\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "色 (いろ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"colour\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "various", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"いろいろ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "いろいろ", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"various\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "うえ (on top of)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"上\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "on top of (うえ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"上\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "上 (うえ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"on top of\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "うしろ (behind)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"後ろ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "behind (うしろ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"後ろ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "後ろ (うしろ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"behind\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "うすい (thin, weak)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"薄い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "thin, weak (うすい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"薄い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "薄い (うすい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"thin, weak\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "うた (song)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"歌\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "song (うた)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"歌\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "歌 (うた)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"song\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "うたう (to sing)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"歌う\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to sing (うたう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"歌う\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "歌う (うたう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to sing\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "うまれる (to be born)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"生まれる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to be born (うまれる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"生まれる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "生まれる (うまれる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to be born\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "うみ (sea)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"海\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "sea (うみ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"海\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "海 (うみ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"sea\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "うる (to sell)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"売る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to sell (うる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"売る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "売る (うる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to sell\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "うるさい (noisy, annoying)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"煩い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "noisy, annoying (うるさい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"煩い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "煩い (うるさい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"noisy, annoying\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "うわぎ (jacket)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"上着\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "jacket (うわぎ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"上着\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "上着 (うわぎ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"jacket\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "え (picture)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"絵\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "picture (え)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"絵\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "絵 (え)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"picture\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "えいが (movie)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"映画\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "movie (えいが)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"映画\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "映画 (えいが)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"movie\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "えいがかん (cinema)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"映画館\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "cinema (えいがかん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"映画館\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "映画館 (えいがかん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"cinema\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "えいご (English language)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"英語\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "English language (えいご)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"英語\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "英語 (えいご)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"English language\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "yes", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ええ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ええ", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"yes\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "えき (station)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"駅\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "station (えき)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"駅\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "駅 (えき)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"station\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "elevator", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"エレベーター\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "エレベーター", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"elevator\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "えんぴつ (pencil)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"鉛筆\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "pencil (えんぴつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"鉛筆\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "鉛筆 (えんぴつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"pencil\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "delicious", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"おいしい\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おいしい", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"delicious\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おおい (many)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"多い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "many (おおい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"多い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "多い (おおい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"many\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おおきい (big)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"大きい\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "big (おおきい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"大きい\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "大きい (おおきい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"big\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おおきな (big)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"大きな\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "big (おおきな)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"大きな\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "大きな (おおきな)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"big\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おおぜい (great number of people)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"大勢\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "great number of people (おおぜい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"大勢\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "大勢 (おおぜい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"great number of people\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おかあさん ((honorable) mother)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"お母さん\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "(honorable) mother (おかあさん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"お母さん\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "お母さん (おかあさん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"(honorable) mother\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おかし (sweets, candy)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"お菓子\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "sweets, candy (おかし)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"お菓子\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "お菓子 (おかし)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"sweets, candy\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おかね (money)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"お金\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "money (おかね)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"お金\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "お金 (おかね)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"money\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おきる (to get up)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"起きる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to get up (おきる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"起きる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "起きる (おきる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to get up\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おく (to put)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"置く\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to put (おく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"置く\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "置く (おく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to put\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おくさん ((honorable) wife)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"奥さん\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "(honorable) wife (おくさん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"奥さん\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "奥さん (おくさん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"(honorable) wife\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おさけ (alcohol, rice wine)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"お酒\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "alcohol, rice wine (おさけ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"お酒\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "お酒 (おさけ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"alcohol, rice wine\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おさら (plate, dish)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"お皿\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "plate, dish (おさら)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"お皿\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "お皿 (おさら)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"plate, dish\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おじいさん (grandfather, male senior citizen)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"伯父/叔父\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "grandfather, male senior citizen (おじいさん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"伯父/叔父\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "伯父/叔父 (おじいさん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"grandfather, male senior citizen\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おしえる (to teach, to tell)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"教える\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to teach, to tell (おしえる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"教える\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "教える (おしえる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to teach, to tell\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おじさん (uncle, middle aged gentleman)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"伯父/叔父\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "uncle, middle aged gentleman (おじさん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"伯父/叔父\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "伯父/叔父 (おじさん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"uncle, middle aged gentleman\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おす (to push, to stamp something)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"押す\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to push, to stamp something (おす)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"押す\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "押す (おす)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to push, to stamp something\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おそい (late, slow)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"遅い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "late, slow (おそい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"遅い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "遅い (おそい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"late, slow\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おちゃ (green tea)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"お茶\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "green tea (おちゃ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"お茶\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "お茶 (おちゃ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"green tea\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おてあらい (bathroom)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"お手洗い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "bathroom (おてあらい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"お手洗い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "お手洗い (おてあらい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"bathroom\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おとうさん ((honorable) father)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"お父さん\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "(honorable) father (おとうさん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"お父さん\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "お父さん (おとうさん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"(honorable) father\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おとうと (younger brother)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"弟\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "younger brother (おとうと)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"弟\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "弟 (おとうと)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"younger brother\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おとこ (man)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"男\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "man (おとこ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"男\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "男 (おとこ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"man\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おとこのこ (boy)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"男の子\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "boy (おとこのこ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"男の子\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "男の子 (おとこのこ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"boy\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おととい (day before yesterday)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"一昨日\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "day before yesterday (おととい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"一昨日\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "一昨日 (おととい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"day before yesterday\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おととし (year before last)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"一昨年\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "year before last (おととし)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"一昨年\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "一昨年 (おととし)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"year before last\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おとな (adult)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"大人\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "adult (おとな)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"大人\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "大人 (おとな)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"adult\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "stomach", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"おなか\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おなか", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"stomach\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おなじ (same)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"同じ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "same (おなじ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"同じ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "同じ (おなじ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"same\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おにいさん ((honorable) older brother)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"お兄さん\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "(honorable) older brother (おにいさん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"お兄さん\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "お兄さん (おにいさん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"(honorable) older brother\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おねえさん ((honorable) older sister)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"お姉さん\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "(honorable) older sister (おねえさん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"お姉さん\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "お姉さん (おねえさん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"(honorable) older sister\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "grandmother, female senior-citizen", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"おばあさん\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おばあさん", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"grandmother, female senior-citizen\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おばさん (aunt)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"伯母さん/叔母さん\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "aunt (おばさん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"伯母さん/叔母さん\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "伯母さん/叔母さん (おばさん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"aunt\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おふろ (bath)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"お風呂\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "bath (おふろ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"お風呂\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "お風呂 (おふろ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"bath\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おべんとう (boxed lunch)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"お弁当\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "boxed lunch (おべんとう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"お弁当\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "お弁当 (おべんとう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"boxed lunch\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おぼえる (to remember)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"覚える\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to remember (おぼえる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"覚える\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "覚える (おぼえる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to remember\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "friendly term for policeman", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"おまわりさん\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おまわりさん", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"friendly term for policeman\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おもい (heavy)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"重い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "heavy (おもい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"重い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "重い (おもい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"heavy\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "interesting", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"おもしろい\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おもしろい", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"interesting\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "およぐ (to swim)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"泳ぐ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to swim (およぐ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"泳ぐ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "泳ぐ (およぐ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to swim\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おりる (to get off, to descend)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"降りる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to get off, to descend (おりる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"降りる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "降りる (おりる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to get off, to descend\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おわる (to finish)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"終る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to finish (おわる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"終る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "終る (おわる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to finish\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おんがく (music)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"音楽\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "music (おんがく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"音楽\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "音楽 (おんがく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"music\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おんな (woman)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"女\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "woman (おんな)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"女\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "女 (おんな)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"woman\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おんなのこ (girl)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"女の子\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "girl (おんなのこ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"女の子\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "女の子 (おんなのこ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"girl\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "がいこく (foreign country)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"外国\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "foreign country (がいこく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"外国\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "外国 (がいこく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"foreign country\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "がいこくじん (foreigner)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"外国人\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "foreigner (がいこくじん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"外国人\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "外国人 (がいこくじん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"foreigner\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かいしゃ (company)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"会社\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "company (かいしゃ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"会社\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "会社 (かいしゃ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"company\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かいだん (stairs)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"階段\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "stairs (かいだん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"階段\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "階段 (かいだん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"stairs\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かいもの (shopping)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"買い物\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "shopping (かいもの)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"買い物\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "買い物 (かいもの)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"shopping\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かう (to buy)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"買う\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to buy (かう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"買う\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "買う (かう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to buy\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かえす (to return something)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"返す\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to return something (かえす)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"返す\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "返す (かえす)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to return something\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かえる (to go back)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"帰る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to go back (かえる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"帰る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "帰る (かえる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to go back\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to take time or money", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"かかる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かかる", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to take time or money\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "key", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"かぎ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かぎ", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"key\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かく (to write)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"書く\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to write (かく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"書く\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "書く (かく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to write\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "がくせい (student)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"学生\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "student (がくせい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"学生\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "学生 (がくせい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"student\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to call by phone", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"かける\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かける", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to call by phone\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かさ (umbrella)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"傘\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "umbrella (かさ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"傘\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "傘 (かさ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"umbrella\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かす (to lend)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"貸す\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to lend (かす)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"貸す\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "貸す (かす)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to lend\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かぜ (wind)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"風\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "wind (かぜ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"風\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "風 (かぜ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"wind\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かぜ (a cold)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"風邪\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "a cold (かぜ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"風邪\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "風邪 (かぜ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"a cold\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かぞく (family)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"家族\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "family (かぞく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"家族\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "家族 (かぞく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"family\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かた (person, way of doing)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"方\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "person, way of doing (かた)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"方\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "方 (かた)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"person, way of doing\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "がっこう (school)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"学校\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "school (がっこう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"学校\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "学校 (がっこう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"school\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "cup", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"カップ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "カップ", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"cup\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かてい (household)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"家庭\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "household (かてい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"家庭\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "家庭 (かてい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"household\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かど (a corner)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"角\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "a corner (かど)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"角\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "角 (かど)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"a corner\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "bag, basket", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"かばん\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かばん", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"bag, basket\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かびん (a vase)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"花瓶\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "a vase (かびん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"花瓶\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "花瓶 (かびん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"a vase\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かみ (paper)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"紙\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "paper (かみ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"紙\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "紙 (かみ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"paper\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "camera", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"カメラ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "カメラ", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"camera\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かようび (Tuesday)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"火曜日\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "Tuesday (かようび)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"火曜日\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "火曜日 (かようび)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"Tuesday\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "からい (spicy)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"辛い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "spicy (からい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"辛い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "辛い (からい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"spicy\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "からだ (body)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"体\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "body (からだ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"体\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "体 (からだ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"body\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かりる (to borrow)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"借りる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to borrow (かりる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"借りる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "借りる (かりる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to borrow\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かるい (light)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"軽い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "light (かるい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"軽い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "軽い (かるい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"light\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "curry", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"カレー\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "カレー", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"curry\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "calendar", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"カレンダー\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "カレンダー", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"calendar\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かわ (river)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"川/河\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "river (かわ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"川/河\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "川/河 (かわ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"river\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "cute", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"かわいい\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かわいい", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"cute\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かんじ (Chinese character)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"漢字\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "Chinese character (かんじ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"漢字\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "漢字 (かんじ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"Chinese character\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "き (tree, wood)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"木\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "tree, wood (き)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"木\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "木 (き)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"tree, wood\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "きいろ (yellow)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"黄色\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "yellow (きいろ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"黄色\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "黄色 (きいろ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"yellow\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "きいろい (yellow)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"黄色い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "yellow (きいろい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"黄色い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "黄色い (きいろい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"yellow\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "きえる (to disappear)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"消える\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to disappear (きえる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"消える\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "消える (きえる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to disappear\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "きく (to hear, to listen to, to ask)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"聞く\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to hear, to listen to, to ask (きく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"聞く\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "聞く (きく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to hear, to listen to, to ask\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "きた (north)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"北\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "north (きた)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"北\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "北 (きた)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"north\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "guitar", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ギター\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ギター", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"guitar\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "きたない (dirty)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"汚い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "dirty (きたない)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"汚い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "汚い (きたない)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"dirty\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "きっさてん (coffee lounge)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"喫茶店\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "coffee lounge (きっさてん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"喫茶店\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "喫茶店 (きっさてん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"coffee lounge\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "きって (postage stamp)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"切手\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "postage stamp (きって)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"切手\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "切手 (きって)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"postage stamp\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "きっぷ (ticket)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"切符\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ticket (きっぷ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"切符\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "切符 (きっぷ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"ticket\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "きのう (yesterday)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"昨日\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "yesterday (きのう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"昨日\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "昨日 (きのう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"yesterday\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "きゅう / く (nine)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"九\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "nine (きゅう / く)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"九\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "九 (きゅう / く)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"nine\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ぎゅうにく (beef)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"牛肉\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "beef (ぎゅうにく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"牛肉\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "牛肉 (ぎゅうにく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"beef\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ぎゅうにゅう (milk)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"牛乳\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "milk (ぎゅうにゅう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"牛乳\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "牛乳 (ぎゅうにゅう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"milk\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "きょう (today)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"今日\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "today (きょう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"今日\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "今日 (きょう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"today\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "きょうしつ (classroom)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"教室\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "classroom (きょうしつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"教室\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "教室 (きょうしつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"classroom\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "きょうだい ((humble) siblings)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"兄弟\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "(humble) siblings (きょうだい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"兄弟\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "兄弟 (きょうだい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"(humble) siblings\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "きょねん (last year)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"去年\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "last year (きょねん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"去年\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "去年 (きょねん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"last year\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "きらい (hate)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"嫌い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "hate (きらい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"嫌い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "嫌い (きらい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"hate\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "きる (to cut)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"切る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to cut (きる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"切る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "切る (きる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to cut\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "きる (to put on from the shoulders down)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"着る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to put on from the shoulders down (きる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"着る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "着る (きる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to put on from the shoulders down\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "pretty, clean", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"きれい\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "きれい", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"pretty, clean\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "kilogram", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"キロ/キログラム\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "キロ/キログラム", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"kilogram\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "kilometre", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"キロ/キロメートル\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "キロ/キロメートル", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"kilometre\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ぎんこう (bank)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"銀行\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "bank (ぎんこう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"銀行\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "銀行 (ぎんこう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"bank\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "きんようび (Friday)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"金曜日\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "Friday (きんようび)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"金曜日\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "金曜日 (きんようび)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"Friday\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "くすり (medicine)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"薬\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "medicine (くすり)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"薬\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "薬 (くすり)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"medicine\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "please", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ください\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ください", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"please\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "くだもの (fruit)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"果物\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "fruit (くだもの)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"果物\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "果物 (くだもの)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"fruit\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "くち (mouth, opening)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"口\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "mouth, opening (くち)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"口\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "口 (くち)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"mouth, opening\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "くつ (shoes)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"靴\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "shoes (くつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"靴\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "靴 (くつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"shoes\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "くつした (socks)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"靴下\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "socks (くつした)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"靴下\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "靴下 (くつした)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"socks\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "くに (country)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"国\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "country (くに)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"国\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "国 (くに)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"country\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "くもり (cloudy weather)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"曇り\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "cloudy weather (くもり)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"曇り\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "曇り (くもり)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"cloudy weather\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "くもる (to become cloudy, to become dim)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"曇る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to become cloudy, to become dim (くもる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"曇る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "曇る (くもる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to become cloudy, to become dim\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "くらい (gloomy)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"暗い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "gloomy (くらい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"暗い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "暗い (くらい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"gloomy\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "class", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"クラス\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "クラス", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"class\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "gram", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"グラム\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "グラム", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"gram\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "くる (to come)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"来る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to come (くる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"来る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "来る (くる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to come\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "くるま (car, vehicle)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"車\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "car, vehicle (くるま)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"車\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "車 (くるま)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"car, vehicle\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "くろ (black)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"黒\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "black (くろ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"黒\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "黒 (くろ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"black\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "くろい (black)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"黒い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "black (くろい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"黒い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "黒い (くろい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"black\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "けいかん (policeman)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"警官\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "policeman (けいかん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"警官\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "警官 (けいかん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"policeman\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "けさ (this morning)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"今朝\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "this morning (けさ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"今朝\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "今朝 (けさ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"this morning\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "けす (to erase, to turn off power)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"消す\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to erase, to turn off power (けす)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"消す\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "消す (けす)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to erase, to turn off power\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "けっこう (splendid, enough)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"結構\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "splendid, enough (けっこう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"結構\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "結構 (けっこう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"splendid, enough\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "けっこん (marriage)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"結婚\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "marriage (けっこん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"結婚\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "結婚 (けっこん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"marriage\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "げつようび (Monday)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"月曜日\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "Monday (げつようび)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"月曜日\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "月曜日 (げつようび)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"Monday\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "げんかん (entry hall)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"玄関\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "entry hall (げんかん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"玄関\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "玄関 (げんかん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"entry hall\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "げんき (health, vitality)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"元気\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "health, vitality (げんき)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"元気\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "元気 (げんき)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"health, vitality\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ご (five)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"五\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "five (ご)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"五\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "五 (ご)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"five\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "こうえん (park)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"公園\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "park (こうえん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"公園\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "公園 (こうえん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"park\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "こうさてん (intersection)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"交差点\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "intersection (こうさてん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"交差点\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "交差点 (こうさてん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"intersection\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "こうちゃ (black tea)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"紅茶\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "black tea (こうちゃ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"紅茶\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "紅茶 (こうちゃ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"black tea\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "こうばん (police box)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"交番\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "police box (こうばん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"交番\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "交番 (こうばん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"police box\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "こえ (voice)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"声\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "voice (こえ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"声\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "声 (こえ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"voice\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "coat, tennis court", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"コート\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "コート", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"coat, tennis court\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "coffee", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"コーヒー\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "コーヒー", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"coffee\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "here", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ここ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ここ", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"here\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ごご (afternoon)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"午後\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "afternoon (ごご)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"午後\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "午後 (ごご)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"afternoon\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ここのか (nine days, ninth day)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"九日\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "nine days, ninth day (ここのか)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"九日\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "九日 (ここのか)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"nine days, ninth day\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ここのつ (nine)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"九つ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "nine (ここのつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"九つ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "九つ (ここのつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"nine\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ごぜん (morning)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"午前\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "morning (ごぜん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"午前\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "午前 (ごぜん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"morning\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "こたえる (to answer)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"答える\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to answer (こたえる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"答える\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "答える (こたえる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to answer\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "this person or way", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"こちら\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "こちら", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"this person or way\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "this person or way", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"こっち\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "こっち", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"this person or way\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "a glass", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"コップ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "コップ", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"a glass\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ことし (this year)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"今年\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "this year (ことし)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"今年\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "今年 (ことし)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"this year\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ことば (word, language)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"言葉\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "word, language (ことば)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"言葉\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "言葉 (ことば)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"word, language\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "こども (child)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"子供\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "child (こども)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"子供\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "子供 (こども)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"child\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "this", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"この\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "この", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"this\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ごはん (cooked rice, meal)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"御飯\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "cooked rice, meal (ごはん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"御飯\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "御飯 (ごはん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"cooked rice, meal\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to copy", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"コピーする\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "コピーする", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to copy\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "こまる (to be worried)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"困る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to be worried (こまる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"困る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "困る (こまる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to be worried\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "this", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"これ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "これ", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"this\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "こんげつ (this month)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"今月\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "this month (こんげつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"今月\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "今月 (こんげつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"this month\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "こんしゅう (this week)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"今週\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "this week (こんしゅう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"今週\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "今週 (こんしゅう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"this week\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "such", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"こんな\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "こんな", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"such\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "こんばん (this evening)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"今晩\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "this evening (こんばん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"今晩\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "今晩 (こんばん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"this evening\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "well…", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"さあ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "さあ", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"well…\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "さいふ (wallet)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"財布\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "wallet (さいふ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"財布\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "財布 (さいふ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"wallet\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "さかな (fish)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"魚\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "fish (さかな)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"魚\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "魚 (さかな)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"fish\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "さき (the future, previous)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"先\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "the future, previous (さき)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"先\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "先 (さき)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"the future, previous\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "さく (to bloom)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"咲く\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to bloom (さく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"咲く\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "咲く (さく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to bloom\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "さくぶん (composition, writing)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"作文\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "composition, writing (さくぶん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"作文\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "作文 (さくぶん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"composition, writing\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "さす (to stretch out hands, to raise an umbrella)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"差す\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to stretch out hands, to raise an umbrella (さす)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"差す\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "差す (さす)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to stretch out hands, to raise an umbrella\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ざっし (magazine)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"雑誌\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "magazine (ざっし)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"雑誌\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "雑誌 (ざっし)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"magazine\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "さとう (sugar)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"砂糖\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "sugar (さとう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"砂糖\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "砂糖 (さとう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"sugar\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "さむい (cold)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"寒い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "cold (さむい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"寒い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "寒い (さむい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"cold\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "さらいねん (year after next)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"さ来年\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "year after next (さらいねん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"さ来年\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "さ来年 (さらいねん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"year after next\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "さん (three)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"三\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "three (さん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"三\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "三 (さん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"three\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "さんぽする (to stroll)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"散歩\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to stroll (さんぽする)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"散歩\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "散歩 (さんぽする)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to stroll\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "し / よん (four)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"四\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "four (し / よん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"四\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "四 (し / よん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"four\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "しお (salt)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"塩\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "salt (しお)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"塩\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "塩 (しお)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"salt\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "however", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"しかし\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "しかし", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"however\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "じかん (time)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"時間\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "time (じかん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"時間\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "時間 (じかん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"time\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "しごと (job)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"仕事\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "job (しごと)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"仕事\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "仕事 (しごと)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"job\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "じしょ (dictionary)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"辞書\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "dictionary (じしょ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"辞書\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "辞書 (じしょ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"dictionary\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "しずか (quiet)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"静か\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "quiet (しずか)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"静か\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "静か (しずか)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"quiet\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "した (below)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"下\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "below (した)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"下\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "下 (した)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"below\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "しち / なな (seven)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"七\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "seven (しち / なな)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"七\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "七 (しち / なな)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"seven\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "しつもん (question)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"質問\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "question (しつもん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"質問\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "質問 (しつもん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"question\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "じてんしゃ (bicycle)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"自転車\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "bicycle (じてんしゃ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"自転車\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "自転車 (じてんしゃ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"bicycle\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "じどうしゃ (automobile)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"自動車\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "automobile (じどうしゃ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"自動車\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "自動車 (じどうしゃ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"automobile\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "しぬ (to die)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"死ぬ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to die (しぬ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"死ぬ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "死ぬ (しぬ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to die\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "じびき (dictionary)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"字引\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "dictionary (じびき)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"字引\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "字引 (じびき)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"dictionary\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "じぶん (oneself)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"自分\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "oneself (じぶん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"自分\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "自分 (じぶん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"oneself\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "しまる (to close, to be closed)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"閉まる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to close, to be closed (しまる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"閉まる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "閉まる (しまる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to close, to be closed\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "しめる (to close something)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"閉める\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to close something (しめる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"閉める\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "閉める (しめる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to close something\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "しめる (to tie)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"締める\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to tie (しめる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"締める\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "締める (しめる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to tie\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "well then…", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"じゃ/じゃあ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "じゃ/じゃあ", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"well then…\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "しゃしん (photograph)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"写真\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "photograph (しゃしん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"写真\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "写真 (しゃしん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"photograph\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "shirt", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"シャツ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "シャツ", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"shirt\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "shower", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"シャワー\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "シャワー", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"shower\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "じゅう とお (ten)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"十\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ten (じゅう とお)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"十\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "十 (じゅう とお)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"ten\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "じゅぎょう (lesson, class work)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"授業\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "lesson, class work (じゅぎょう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"授業\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "授業 (じゅぎょう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"lesson, class work\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "しゅくだい (homework)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"宿題\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "homework (しゅくだい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"宿題\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "宿題 (しゅくだい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"homework\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "じょうず (skillful)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"上手\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "skillful (じょうず)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"上手\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "上手 (じょうず)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"skillful\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "じょうぶ (strong, durable)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"丈夫\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "strong, durable (じょうぶ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"丈夫\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "丈夫 (じょうぶ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"strong, durable\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "soy sauce", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"しょうゆ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "しょうゆ", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"soy sauce\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "しょくどう (dining hall)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"食堂\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "dining hall (しょくどう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"食堂\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "食堂 (しょくどう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"dining hall\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "しる (to know)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"知る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to know (しる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"知る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "知る (しる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to know\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "しろ (white)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"白\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "white (しろ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"白\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "白 (しろ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"white\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "しろい (white)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"白い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "white (しろい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"白い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "白い (しろい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"white\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "しんぶん (newspaper)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"新聞\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "newspaper (しんぶん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"新聞\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "新聞 (しんぶん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"newspaper\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "すいようび (Wednesday)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"水曜日\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "Wednesday (すいようび)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"水曜日\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "水曜日 (すいようび)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"Wednesday\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "すう (to smoke, to suck)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"吸う\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to smoke, to suck (すう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"吸う\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "吸う (すう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to smoke, to suck\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "skirt", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"スカート\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "スカート", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"skirt\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "すき (likeable)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"好き\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "likeable (すき)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"好き\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "好き (すき)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"likeable\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "すくない (a few)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"少ない\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "a few (すくない)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"少ない\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "少ない (すくない)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"a few\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "instantly", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"すぐに\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "すぐに", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"instantly\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "すこし (few)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"少し\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "few (すこし)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"少し\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "少し (すこし)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"few\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "すずしい (refreshing)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"涼しい\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "refreshing (すずしい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"涼しい\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "涼しい (すずしい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"refreshing\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "heater", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ストーブ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ストーブ", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"heater\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "spoon", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"スプーン\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "スプーン", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"spoon\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "sport", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"スポーツ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "スポーツ", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"sport\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "trousers", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ズボン\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ズボン", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"trousers\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "すむ (to live in)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"住む\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to live in (すむ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"住む\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "住む (すむ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to live in\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "slippers", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"スリッパ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "スリッパ", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"slippers\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to do", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"する\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "する", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to do\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "すわる (to sit)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"座る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to sit (すわる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"座る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "座る (すわる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to sit\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "せ (height, stature)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"背\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "height, stature (せ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"背\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "背 (せ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"height, stature\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "せいと (pupil)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"生徒\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "pupil (せいと)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"生徒\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "生徒 (せいと)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"pupil\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "sweater, jumper", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"セーター\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "セーター", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"sweater, jumper\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "soap", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"せっけん\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "せっけん", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"soap\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "せびろ (business suit)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"背広\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "business suit (せびろ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"背広\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "背広 (せびろ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"business suit\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "せまい (narrow)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"狭い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "narrow (せまい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"狭い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "狭い (せまい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"narrow\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "zero", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ゼロ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ゼロ", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"zero\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "せん (thousand)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"千\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "thousand (せん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"千\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "千 (せん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"thousand\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "せんげつ (last month)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"先月\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "last month (せんげつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"先月\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "先月 (せんげつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"last month\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "せんしゅう (last week)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"先週\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "last week (せんしゅう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"先週\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "先週 (せんしゅう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"last week\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "せんせい (teacher, doctor)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"先生\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "teacher, doctor (せんせい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"先生\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "先生 (せんせい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"teacher, doctor\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "せんたく (washing)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"洗濯\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "washing (せんたく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"洗濯\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "洗濯 (せんたく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"washing\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ぜんぶ (all)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"全部\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "all (ぜんぶ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"全部\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "全部 (ぜんぶ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"all\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "そうじする (to clean, to sweep)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"掃除\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to clean, to sweep (そうじする)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"掃除\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "掃除 (そうじする)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to clean, to sweep\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "and", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"そうして/そして\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "そうして/そして", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"and\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "that place", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"そこ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "そこ", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"that place\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "over there", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"そちら\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "そちら", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"over there\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "over there", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"そっち\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "そっち", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"over there\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "そと (outside)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"外\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "outside (そと)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"外\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "外 (そと)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"outside\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "that", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"その\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "その", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"that\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "near, beside", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"そば\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "そば", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"near, beside\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "そら (sky)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"空\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "sky (そら)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"空\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "空 (そら)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"sky\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "that", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"それ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "それ", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"that\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "after that", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"それから\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "それから", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"after that\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "in that situation", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"それでは\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "それでは", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"in that situation\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "だいがく (university)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"大学\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "university (だいがく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"大学\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "大学 (だいがく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"university\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "たいしかん (embassy)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"大使館\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "embassy (たいしかん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"大使館\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "大使館 (たいしかん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"embassy\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "だいじょうぶ (all right)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"大丈夫\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "all right (だいじょうぶ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"大丈夫\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "大丈夫 (だいじょうぶ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"all right\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "だいすき (to be very likeable)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"大好き\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to be very likeable (だいすき)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"大好き\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "大好き (だいすき)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to be very likeable\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "たいせつ (important)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"大切\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "important (たいせつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"大切\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "大切 (たいせつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"important\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "だいどころ (kitchen)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"台所\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "kitchen (だいどころ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"台所\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "台所 (だいどころ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"kitchen\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "very", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"たいへん\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "たいへん", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"very\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "difficult situation", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"たいへん\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "たいへん", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"difficult situation\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "たかい (tall, expensive)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"高い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "tall, expensive (たかい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"高い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "高い (たかい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"tall, expensive\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "many", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"たくさん\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "たくさん", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"many\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "taxi", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"タクシー\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "タクシー", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"taxi\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "だす (to put out)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"出す\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to put out (だす)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"出す\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "出す (だす)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to put out\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "たつ (to stand)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"立つ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to stand (たつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"立つ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "立つ (たつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to stand\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "length, height", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"たて\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "たて", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"length, height\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "たてもの (building)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"建物\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "building (たてもの)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"建物\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "建物 (たてもの)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"building\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "たのしい (enjoyable)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"楽しい\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "enjoyable (たのしい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"楽しい\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "楽しい (たのしい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"enjoyable\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "たのむ (to ask)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"頼む\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to ask (たのむ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"頼む\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "頼む (たのむ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to ask\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "tobacco, cigarettes", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"たばこ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "たばこ", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"tobacco, cigarettes\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "probably", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"たぶん\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "たぶん", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"probably\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "たべもの (food)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"食べ物\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "food (たべもの)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"食べ物\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "食べ物 (たべもの)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"food\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "たべる (to eat)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"食べる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to eat (たべる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"食べる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "食べる (たべる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to eat\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "たまご (egg)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"卵\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "egg (たまご)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"卵\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "卵 (たまご)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"egg\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "だれ (who)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"誰\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "who (だれ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"誰\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "誰 (だれ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"who\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "だれか (somebody)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"誰\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "somebody (だれか)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"誰\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "誰 (だれか)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"somebody\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "たんじょうび (birthday)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"誕生日\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "birthday (たんじょうび)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"誕生日\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "誕生日 (たんじょうび)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"birthday\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "gradually", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"だんだん\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "だんだん", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"gradually\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ちいさい (little)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"小さい\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "little (ちいさい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"小さい\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "小さい (ちいさい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"little\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ちいさな (little)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"小さな\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "little (ちいさな)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"小さな\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "小さな (ちいさな)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"little\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ちかい (near)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"近い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "near (ちかい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"近い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "近い (ちかい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"near\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ちがう (to differ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"違う\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to differ (ちがう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"違う\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "違う (ちがう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to differ\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ちかく (near)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"近く\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "near (ちかく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"近く\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "近く (ちかく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"near\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ちかてつ (underground train)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"地下鉄\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "underground train (ちかてつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"地下鉄\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "地下鉄 (ちかてつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"underground train\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ちず (map)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"地図\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "map (ちず)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"地図\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "地図 (ちず)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"map\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ちゃいろ (brown)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"茶色\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "brown (ちゃいろ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"茶色\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "茶色 (ちゃいろ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"brown\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "rice bowl", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ちゃわん\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ちゃわん", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"rice bowl\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "exactly", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ちょうど\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ちょうど", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"exactly\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "somewhat", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ちょっと\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ちょっと", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"somewhat\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ついたち (first of month)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"一日\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "first of month (ついたち)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"一日\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "一日 (ついたち)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"first of month\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "つかう (to use)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"使う\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to use (つかう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"使う\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "使う (つかう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to use\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "つかれる (to get tired)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"疲れる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to get tired (つかれる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"疲れる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "疲れる (つかれる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to get tired\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "つぎ (next)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"次\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "next (つぎ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"次\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "次 (つぎ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"next\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "つく (to arrive at)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"着く\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to arrive at (つく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"着く\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "着く (つく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to arrive at\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "つくえ (desk)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"机\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "desk (つくえ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"机\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "机 (つくえ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"desk\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "つくる (to make)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"作る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to make (つくる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"作る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "作る (つくる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to make\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to turn on", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"つける\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "つける", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to turn on\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "つとめる (to work for someone)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"勤める\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to work for someone (つとめる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"勤める\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "勤める (つとめる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to work for someone\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "boring", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"つまらない\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "つまらない", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"boring\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "つめたい (cold to the touch)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"冷たい\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "cold to the touch (つめたい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"冷たい\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "冷たい (つめたい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"cold to the touch\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "つよい (powerful)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"強い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "powerful (つよい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"強い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "強い (つよい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"powerful\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "て (hand)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"手\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "hand (て)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"手\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "手 (て)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"hand\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "tape", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"テープ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "テープ", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"tape\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "table", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"テーブル\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "テーブル", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"table\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "tape recorder", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"テープレコーダー\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "テープレコーダー", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"tape recorder\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "でかける (to go out)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"出かける\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to go out (でかける)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"出かける\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "出かける (でかける)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to go out\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "てがみ (letter)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"手紙\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "letter (てがみ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"手紙\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "手紙 (てがみ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"letter\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to be able to", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"できる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "できる", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to be able to\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "でぐち (exit)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"出口\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "exit (でぐち)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"出口\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "出口 (でぐち)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"exit\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "test", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"テスト\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "テスト", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"test\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "with that...", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"では\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "では", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"with that...\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "department store", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"デパート\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "デパート", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"department store\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "but", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"でも\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "でも", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"but\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "でる (to appear, to leave)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"出る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to appear, to leave (でる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"出る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "出る (でる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to appear, to leave\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "television", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"テレビ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "テレビ", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"television\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "てんき (weather)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"天気\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "weather (てんき)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"天気\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "天気 (てんき)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"weather\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "でんき (electricity, electric light)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"電気\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "electricity, electric light (でんき)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"電気\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "電気 (でんき)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"electricity, electric light\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "でんしゃ (electric train)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"電車\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "electric train (でんしゃ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"電車\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "電車 (でんしゃ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"electric train\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "でんわ (telephone)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"電話\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "telephone (でんわ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"電話\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "電話 (でんわ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"telephone\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "と (Japanese style door)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"戸\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "Japanese style door (と)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"戸\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "戸 (と)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"Japanese style door\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "Western style door", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ドア\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ドア", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"Western style door\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "toilet", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"トイレ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "トイレ", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"toilet\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "how, in what way", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"どう\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "どう", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"how, in what way\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "for what reason", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"どうして\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "どうして", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"for what reason\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "please", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"どうぞ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "どうぞ", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"please\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "どうぶつ (animal)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"動物\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "animal (どうぶつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"動物\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "動物 (どうぶつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"animal\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "thanks", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"どうも\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "どうも", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"thanks\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "とおい (far)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"遠い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "far (とおい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"遠い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "遠い (とおい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"far\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "とおか (ten days, the tenth day)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"十日\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ten days, the tenth day (とおか)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"十日\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "十日 (とおか)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"ten days, the tenth day\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ときどき (sometimes)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"時々\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "sometimes (ときどき)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"時々\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "時々 (ときどき)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"sometimes\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "とけい (watch, clock)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"時計\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "watch, clock (とけい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"時計\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "時計 (とけい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"watch, clock\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "where", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"どこ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "どこ", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"where\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ところ (place)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"所\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "place (ところ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"所\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "所 (ところ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"place\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "とし (year)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"年\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "year (とし)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"年\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "年 (とし)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"year\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "としょかん (library)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"図書館\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "library (としょかん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"図書館\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "図書館 (としょかん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"library\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "which of two", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"どちら\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "どちら", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"which of two\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "which", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"どっち\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "どっち", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"which\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "very", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"とても\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "とても", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"very\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "who", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"どなた\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "どなた", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"who\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "となり (next door to)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"隣\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "next door to (となり)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"隣\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "隣 (となり)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"next door to\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "which", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"どの\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "どの", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"which\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "とぶ (to fly, to hop)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"飛ぶ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to fly, to hop (とぶ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"飛ぶ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "飛ぶ (とぶ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to fly, to hop\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "とまる (to come to a halt)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"止まる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to come to a halt (とまる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"止まる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "止まる (とまる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to come to a halt\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ともだち (friend)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"友達\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "friend (ともだち)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"友達\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "友達 (ともだち)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"friend\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "どようび (Saturday)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"土曜日\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "Saturday (どようび)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"土曜日\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "土曜日 (どようび)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"Saturday\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "とり (bird)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"鳥\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "bird (とり)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"鳥\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "鳥 (とり)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"bird\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "とりにく (chicken meat)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"とり肉\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "chicken meat (とりにく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"とり肉\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "とり肉 (とりにく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"chicken meat\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "とる (to take something)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"取る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to take something (とる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"取る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "取る (とる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to take something\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "とる (to take a photo or record a film)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"撮る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to take a photo or record a film (とる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"撮る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "撮る (とる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to take a photo or record a film\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "which (of three or more)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"どれ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "どれ", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"which (of three or more)\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "knife", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ナイフ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ナイフ", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"knife\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "なか (middle)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"中\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "middle (なか)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"中\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "中 (なか)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"middle\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ながい (long)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"長い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "long (ながい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"長い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "長い (ながい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"long\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "なく (animal noise. to chirp, roar or croak etc.)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"鳴く\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "animal noise. to chirp, roar or croak etc. (なく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"鳴く\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "鳴く (なく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"animal noise. to chirp, roar or croak etc.\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "なくす (to lose something)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"無くす\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to lose something (なくす)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"無くす\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "無くす (なくす)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to lose something\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "why", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"なぜ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "なぜ", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"why\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "なつ (summer)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"夏\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "summer (なつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"夏\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "夏 (なつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"summer\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "なつやすみ (summer holiday)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"夏休み\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "summer holiday (なつやすみ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"夏休み\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "夏休み (なつやすみ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"summer holiday\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "et cetera", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"など\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "など", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"et cetera\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ななつ (seven)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"七つ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "seven (ななつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"七つ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "七つ (ななつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"seven\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "なのか (seven days, the seventh day)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"七日\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "seven days, the seventh day (なのか)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"七日\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "七日 (なのか)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"seven days, the seventh day\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "なまえ (name)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"名前\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "name (なまえ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"名前\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "名前 (なまえ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"name\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ならう (to learn)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"習う\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to learn (ならう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"習う\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "習う (ならう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to learn\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ならぶ (to line up, to stand in a line)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"並ぶ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to line up, to stand in a line (ならぶ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"並ぶ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "並ぶ (ならぶ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to line up, to stand in a line\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ならべる (to line up, to set up)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"並べる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to line up, to set up (ならべる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"並べる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "並べる (ならべる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to line up, to set up\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to become", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"なる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "なる", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to become\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "なん/なに (what)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"何\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "what (なん/なに)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"何\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "何 (なん/なに)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"what\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "に (two)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"二\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "two (に)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"二\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "二 (に)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"two\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "にぎやか (bustling, busy)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"賑やか\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "bustling, busy (にぎやか)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"賑やか\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "賑やか (にぎやか)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"bustling, busy\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "にく (meat)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"肉\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "meat (にく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"肉\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "肉 (にく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"meat\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "にし (west)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"西\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "west (にし)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"西\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "西 (にし)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"west\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "にちようび (Sunday)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"日曜日\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "Sunday (にちようび)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"日曜日\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "日曜日 (にちようび)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"Sunday\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "にもつ (luggage)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"荷物\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "luggage (にもつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"荷物\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "荷物 (にもつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"luggage\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "news", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ニュース\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ニュース", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"news\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "にわ (garden)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"庭\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "garden (にわ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"庭\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "庭 (にわ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"garden\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ぬぐ (to take off clothes)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"脱ぐ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to take off clothes (ぬぐ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"脱ぐ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "脱ぐ (ぬぐ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to take off clothes\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ぬるい (luke warm)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"温い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "luke warm (ぬるい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"温い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "温い (ぬるい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"luke warm\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "tie, necktie", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ネクタイ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ネクタイ", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"tie, necktie\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ねこ (cat)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"猫\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "cat (ねこ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"猫\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "猫 (ねこ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"cat\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ねる (to go to bed, to sleep)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"寝る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to go to bed, to sleep (ねる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"寝る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "寝る (ねる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to go to bed, to sleep\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "notebook, exercise book", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ノート\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ノート", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"notebook, exercise book\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "のぼる (to climb)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"登る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to climb (のぼる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"登る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "登る (のぼる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to climb\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "のみもの (a drink)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"飲み物\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "a drink (のみもの)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"飲み物\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "飲み物 (のみもの)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"a drink\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "のむ (to drink)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"飲む\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to drink (のむ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"飲む\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "飲む (のむ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to drink\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "のる (to get on, to ride)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"乗る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to get on, to ride (のる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"乗る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "乗る (のる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to get on, to ride\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "は (tooth)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"歯\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "tooth (は)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"歯\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "歯 (は)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"tooth\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "party", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"パーティー\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "パーティー", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"party\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "yes", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"はい\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "はい", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"yes\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "はいざら (ashtray)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"灰皿\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ashtray (はいざら)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"灰皿\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "灰皿 (はいざら)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"ashtray\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "はいる (to enter, to contain)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"入る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to enter, to contain (はいる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"入る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "入る (はいる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to enter, to contain\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "はがき (postcard)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"葉書\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "postcard (はがき)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"葉書\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "葉書 (はがき)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"postcard\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to wear, to put on trousers", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"はく\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "はく", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to wear, to put on trousers\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "はこ (box)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"箱\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "box (はこ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"箱\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "箱 (はこ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"box\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "はし (bridge)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"橋\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "bridge (はし)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"橋\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "橋 (はし)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"bridge\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "chopsticks", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"はし\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "はし", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"chopsticks\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "はじまる (to begin)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"始まる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to begin (はじまる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"始まる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "始まる (はじまる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to begin\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "はじめ (beginning)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"初め/始め\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "beginning (はじめ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"初め/始め\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "初め/始め (はじめ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"beginning\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "はじめて (for the first time)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"初めて\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "for the first time (はじめて)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"初めて\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "初めて (はじめて)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"for the first time\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "はしる (to run)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"走る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to run (はしる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"走る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "走る (はしる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to run\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "bus", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"バス\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "バス", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"bus\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "butter", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"バター\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "バター", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"butter\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "はたち (20 years old, 20th year)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"二十歳\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "20 years old, 20th year (はたち)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"二十歳\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "二十歳 (はたち)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"20 years old, 20th year\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "はたらく (to work)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"働く\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to work (はたらく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"働く\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "働く (はたらく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to work\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "はち (eight)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"八\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "eight (はち)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"八\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "八 (はち)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"eight\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "はつか (twenty days, twentieth)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"二十日\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "twenty days, twentieth (はつか)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"二十日\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "二十日 (はつか)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"twenty days, twentieth\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "はな (flower)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"花\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "flower (はな)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"花\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "花 (はな)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"flower\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "はな (nose)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"鼻\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "nose (はな)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"鼻\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "鼻 (はな)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"nose\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "はなし (talk, story)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"話\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "talk, story (はなし)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"話\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "話 (はなし)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"talk, story\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "はなす (to speak)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"話す\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to speak (はなす)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"話す\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "話す (はなす)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to speak\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "はやい (early)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"早い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "early (はやい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"早い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "早い (はやい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"early\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "はやい (quick)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"速い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "quick (はやい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"速い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "速い (はやい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"quick\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "はる (spring)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"春\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "spring (はる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"春\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "春 (はる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"spring\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "はる (to stick)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"貼る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to stick (はる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"貼る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "貼る (はる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to stick\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "はれ (clear weather)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"晴れ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "clear weather (はれ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"晴れ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "晴れ (はれ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"clear weather\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "はれる (to be sunny)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"晴れる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to be sunny (はれる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"晴れる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "晴れる (はれる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to be sunny\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "はん (half)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"半\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "half (はん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"半\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "半 (はん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"half\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ばん (evening)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"晩\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "evening (ばん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"晩\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "晩 (ばん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"evening\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "bread", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"パン\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "パン", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"bread\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "handkerchief", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ハンカチ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ハンカチ", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"handkerchief\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ばんごう (number)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"番号\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "number (ばんごう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"番号\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "番号 (ばんごう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"number\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ばんごはん (evening meal)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"晩御飯\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "evening meal (ばんごはん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"晩御飯\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "晩御飯 (ばんごはん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"evening meal\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "はんぶん (half minute)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"半分\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "half minute (はんぶん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"半分\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "半分 (はんぶん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"half minute\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ひがし (east)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"東\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "east (ひがし)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"東\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "東 (ひがし)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"east\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ひく (to pull)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"引く\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to pull (ひく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"引く\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "引く (ひく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to pull\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ひく (to play an instrument with strings, including piano)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"弾く\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to play an instrument with strings, including piano (ひく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"弾く\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "弾く (ひく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to play an instrument with strings, including piano\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ひくい (short, low)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"低い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "short, low (ひくい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"低い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "低い (ひくい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"short, low\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ひこうき (aeroplane)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"飛行機\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "aeroplane (ひこうき)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"飛行機\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "飛行機 (ひこうき)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"aeroplane\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ひだり (left hand side)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"左\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "left hand side (ひだり)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"左\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "左 (ひだり)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"left hand side\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ひと (person)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"人\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "person (ひと)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"人\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "人 (ひと)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"person\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ひとつ (one)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"一つ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "one (ひとつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"一つ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "一つ (ひとつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"one\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ひとつき (one month)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"一月\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "one month (ひとつき)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"一月\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "一月 (ひとつき)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"one month\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ひとり (one person)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"一人\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "one person (ひとり)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"一人\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "一人 (ひとり)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"one person\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ひま (free time)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"暇\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "free time (ひま)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"暇\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "暇 (ひま)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"free time\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ひゃく (hundred)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"百\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "hundred (ひゃく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"百\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "百 (ひゃく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"hundred\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "びょういん (hospital)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"病院\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "hospital (びょういん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"病院\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "病院 (びょういん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"hospital\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "びょうき (illness)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"病気\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "illness (びょうき)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"病気\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "病気 (びょうき)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"illness\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ひる (noon, daytime)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"昼\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "noon, daytime (ひる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"昼\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "昼 (ひる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"noon, daytime\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ひるごはん (midday meal)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"昼御飯\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "midday meal (ひるごはん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"昼御飯\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "昼御飯 (ひるごはん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"midday meal\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ひろい (spacious, wide)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"広い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "spacious, wide (ひろい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"広い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "広い (ひろい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"spacious, wide\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "roll of film", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"フィルム\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "フィルム", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"roll of film\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ふうとう (envelope)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"封筒\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "envelope (ふうとう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"封筒\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "封筒 (ふうとう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"envelope\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "swimming pool", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"プール\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "プール", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"swimming pool\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "fork", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"フォーク\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "フォーク", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"fork\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ふく (to blow)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"吹く\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to blow (ふく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"吹く\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "吹く (ふく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to blow\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ふく (clothes)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"服\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "clothes (ふく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"服\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "服 (ふく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"clothes\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ふたつ (two)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"二つ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "two (ふたつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"二つ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "二つ (ふたつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"two\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ぶたにく (pork)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"豚肉\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "pork (ぶたにく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"豚肉\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "豚肉 (ぶたにく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"pork\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ふたり (two people)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"二人\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "two people (ふたり)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"二人\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "二人 (ふたり)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"two people\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ふつか (two days, second day of the month)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"二日\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "two days, second day of the month (ふつか)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"二日\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "二日 (ふつか)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"two days, second day of the month\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ふとい (fat)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"太い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "fat (ふとい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"太い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "太い (ふとい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"fat\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ふゆ (winter)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"冬\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "winter (ふゆ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"冬\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "冬 (ふゆ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"winter\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ふる (to fall, e.g. rain or snow)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"降る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to fall, e.g. rain or snow (ふる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"降る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "降る (ふる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to fall, e.g. rain or snow\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ふるい (old (not used for people))", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"古い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "old (not used for people) (ふるい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"古い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "古い (ふるい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"old (not used for people)\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "bath", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ふろ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ふろ", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"bath\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ぶんしょう (sentence, text)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"文章\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "sentence, text (ぶんしょう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"文章\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "文章 (ぶんしょう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"sentence, text\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "page", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ページ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ページ", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"page\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "へた (unskillful)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"下手\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "unskillful (へた)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"下手\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "下手 (へた)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"unskillful\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "bed", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ベッド\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ベッド", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"bed\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "pet", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ペット\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ペット", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"pet\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "へや (room)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"部屋\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "room (へや)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"部屋\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "部屋 (へや)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"room\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "へん (area)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"辺\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "area (へん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"辺\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "辺 (へん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"area\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "pen", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ペン\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ペン", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"pen\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "べんきょうする (to study)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"勉強\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to study (べんきょうする)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"勉強\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "勉強 (べんきょうする)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to study\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "べんり (useful, convenient)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"便利\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "useful, convenient (べんり)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"便利\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "便利 (べんり)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"useful, convenient\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ぼうし (hat)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"帽子\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "hat (ぼうし)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"帽子\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "帽子 (ぼうし)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"hat\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ball-point pen", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ボールペン\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ボールペン", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"ball-point pen\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "other, the rest", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ほか\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ほか", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"other, the rest\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "pocket", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ポケット\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ポケット", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"pocket\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ほしい (want)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"欲しい\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "want (ほしい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"欲しい\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "欲しい (ほしい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"want\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "post", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ポスト\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ポスト", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"post\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ほそい (thin)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"細い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "thin (ほそい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"細い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "細い (ほそい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"thin\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "button", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ボタン\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ボタン", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"button\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "hotel", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ホテル\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ホテル", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"hotel\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ほん (book)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"本\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "book (ほん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"本\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "本 (ほん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"book\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ほんだな (bookshelves)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"本棚\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "bookshelves (ほんだな)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"本棚\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "本棚 (ほんだな)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"bookshelves\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "truth", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ほんとう\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ほんとう", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"truth\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "まいあさ (every morning)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"毎朝\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "every morning (まいあさ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"毎朝\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "毎朝 (まいあさ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"every morning\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "まいげつ/まいつき (every month)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"毎月\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "every month (まいげつ/まいつき)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"毎月\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "毎月 (まいげつ/まいつき)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"every month\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "まいしゅう (every week)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"毎週\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "every week (まいしゅう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"毎週\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "毎週 (まいしゅう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"every week\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "まいにち (every day)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"毎日\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "every day (まいにち)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"毎日\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "毎日 (まいにち)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"every day\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "まいねん/まいとし (every year)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"毎年\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "every year (まいねん/まいとし)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"毎年\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "毎年 (まいねん/まいとし)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"every year\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "まいばん (every night)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"毎晩\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "every night (まいばん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"毎晩\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "毎晩 (まいばん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"every night\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "まえ (before)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"前\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "before (まえ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"前\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "前 (まえ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"before\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "まがる (to turn, to bend)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"曲る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to turn, to bend (まがる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"曲る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "曲る (まがる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to turn, to bend\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "unpleasant", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"まずい\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "まずい", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"unpleasant\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "again, and", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"また\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "また", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"again, and\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "yet, still", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"まだ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "まだ", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"yet, still\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "まち (town, city)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"町\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "town, city (まち)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"町\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "町 (まち)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"town, city\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "まつ (to wait)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"待つ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to wait (まつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"待つ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "待つ (まつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to wait\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "straight ahead, direct", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"まっすぐ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "まっすぐ", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"straight ahead, direct\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "match", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"マッチ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "マッチ", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"match\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "まど (window)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"窓\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "window (まど)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"窓\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "窓 (まど)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"window\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "まるい (round, circular)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"丸い/円い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "round, circular (まるい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"丸い/円い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "丸い/円い (まるい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"round, circular\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "まん (ten thousand)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"万\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ten thousand (まん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"万\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "万 (まん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"ten thousand\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "まんねんひつ (fountain pen)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"万年筆\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "fountain pen (まんねんひつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"万年筆\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "万年筆 (まんねんひつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"fountain pen\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "みがく (to brush teeth, to polish)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"磨く\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to brush teeth, to polish (みがく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"磨く\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "磨く (みがく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to brush teeth, to polish\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "みぎ (right side)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"右\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "right side (みぎ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"右\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "右 (みぎ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"right side\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "みじかい (short)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"短い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "short (みじかい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"短い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "短い (みじかい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"short\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "みず (water)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"水\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "water (みず)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"水\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "水 (みず)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"water\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "みせ (shop)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"店\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "shop (みせ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"店\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "店 (みせ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"shop\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "みせる (to show)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"見せる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to show (みせる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"見せる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "見せる (みせる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to show\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "みち (street)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"道\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "street (みち)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"道\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "道 (みち)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"street\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "みっか (three days, third day of the month)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"三日\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "three days, third day of the month (みっか)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"三日\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "三日 (みっか)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"three days, third day of the month\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "みっつ (three)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"三つ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "three (みっつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"三つ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "三つ (みっつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"three\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "みどり (green)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"緑\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "green (みどり)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"緑\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "緑 (みどり)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"green\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "みなさん (everyone)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"皆さん\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "everyone (みなさん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"皆さん\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "皆さん (みなさん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"everyone\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "みなみ (south)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"南\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "south (みなみ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"南\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "南 (みなみ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"south\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "みみ (ear)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"耳\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ear (みみ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"耳\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "耳 (みみ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"ear\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "みる (to see, to watch)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"見る 観る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to see, to watch (みる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"見る 観る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "見る 観る (みる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to see, to watch\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "everyone", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"みんな\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "みんな", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"everyone\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "むいか (six days, sixth day of the month)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"六日\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "six days, sixth day of the month (むいか)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"六日\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "六日 (むいか)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"six days, sixth day of the month\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "むこう (over there)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"向こう\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "over there (むこう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"向こう\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "向こう (むこう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"over there\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "むずかしい (difficult)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"難しい\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "difficult (むずかしい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"難しい\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "難しい (むずかしい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"difficult\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "むっつ (six)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"六つ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "six (むっつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"六つ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "六つ (むっつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"six\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "むら (village)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"村\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "village (むら)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"村\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "村 (むら)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"village\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "め (eye)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"目\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "eye (め)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"目\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "目 (め)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"eye\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "metre", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"メートル\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "メートル", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"metre\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "めがね (glasses)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"眼鏡\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "glasses (めがね)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"眼鏡\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "眼鏡 (めがね)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"glasses\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "already", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"もう\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "もう", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"already\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "もういちど (again)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"もう一度\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "again (もういちど)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"もう一度\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "もう一度 (もういちど)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"again\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "もくようび (Thursday)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"木曜日\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "Thursday (もくようび)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"木曜日\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "木曜日 (もくようび)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"Thursday\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "もつ (to hold)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"持つ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to hold (もつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"持つ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "持つ (もつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to hold\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "more", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"もっと\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "もっと", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"more\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "もの (thing)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"物\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "thing (もの)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"物\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "物 (もの)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"thing\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "もん (gate)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"門\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "gate (もん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"門\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "門 (もん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"gate\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "もんだい (problem)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"問題\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "problem (もんだい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"問題\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "問題 (もんだい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"problem\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "やおや (greengrocer)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"八百屋\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "greengrocer (やおや)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"八百屋\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "八百屋 (やおや)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"greengrocer\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "やさい (vegetable)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"野菜\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "vegetable (やさい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"野菜\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "野菜 (やさい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"vegetable\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "やさしい (easy, simple)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"易しい\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "easy, simple (やさしい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"易しい\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "易しい (やさしい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"easy, simple\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "やすい (cheap)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"安い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "cheap (やすい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"安い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "安い (やすい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"cheap\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "やすみ (rest, holiday)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"休み\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "rest, holiday (やすみ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"休み\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "休み (やすみ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"rest, holiday\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "やすむ (to rest)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"休む\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to rest (やすむ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"休む\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "休む (やすむ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to rest\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "やっつ (eight)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"八つ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "eight (やっつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"八つ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "八つ (やっつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"eight\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "やま (mountain)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"山\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "mountain (やま)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"山\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "山 (やま)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"mountain\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to do", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"やる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "やる", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to do\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ゆうがた (evening)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"夕方\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "evening (ゆうがた)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"夕方\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "夕方 (ゆうがた)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"evening\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ゆうはん (dinner)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"夕飯\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "dinner (ゆうはん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"夕飯\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "夕飯 (ゆうはん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"dinner\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ゆうびんきょく (post office)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"郵便局\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "post office (ゆうびんきょく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"郵便局\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "郵便局 (ゆうびんきょく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"post office\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ゆうべ (last night)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"昨夜\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "last night (ゆうべ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"昨夜\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "昨夜 (ゆうべ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"last night\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ゆうめい (famous)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"有名\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "famous (ゆうめい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"有名\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "有名 (ゆうめい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"famous\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ゆき (snow)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"雪\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "snow (ゆき)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"雪\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "雪 (ゆき)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"snow\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ゆく (to go)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"行く\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to go (ゆく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"行く\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "行く (ゆく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to go\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "slowly", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ゆっくりと\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ゆっくりと", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"slowly\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ようか (eight days, eighth day of the month)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"八日\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "eight days, eighth day of the month (ようか)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"八日\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "八日 (ようか)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"eight days, eighth day of the month\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ようふく (western-style clothes)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"洋服\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "western-style clothes (ようふく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"洋服\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "洋服 (ようふく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"western-style clothes\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "often, well", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"よく\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "よく", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"often, well\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "よこ (beside, side, width)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"横\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "beside, side, width (よこ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"横\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "横 (よこ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"beside, side, width\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "よっか (four days, fouth day of the month)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"四日\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "four days, fouth day of the month (よっか)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"四日\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "四日 (よっか)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"four days, fouth day of the month\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "よっつ (four)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"四つ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "four (よっつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"四つ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "四つ (よっつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"four\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "よぶ (to call out, to invite)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"呼ぶ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to call out, to invite (よぶ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"呼ぶ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "呼ぶ (よぶ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to call out, to invite\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "よむ (to read)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"読む\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to read (よむ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"読む\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "読む (よむ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to read\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "よる (evening, night)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"夜\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "evening, night (よる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"夜\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "夜 (よる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"evening, night\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "よわい (weak)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"弱い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "weak (よわい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"弱い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "弱い (よわい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"weak\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "らいげつ (next month)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"来月\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "next month (らいげつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"来月\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "来月 (らいげつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"next month\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "らいしゅう (next week)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"来週\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "next week (らいしゅう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"来週\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "来週 (らいしゅう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"next week\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "らいねん (next year)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"来年\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "next year (らいねん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"来年\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "来年 (らいねん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"next year\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "radio", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ラジオ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ラジオ", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"radio\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "radio cassette player", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ラジカセ / ラジオカセット\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ラジカセ / ラジオカセット", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"radio cassette player\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "splendid", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"りっぱ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "りっぱ", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"splendid\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "りゅうがくせい (overseas student)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"留学生\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "overseas student (りゅうがくせい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"留学生\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "留学生 (りゅうがくせい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"overseas student\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "りょうしん (both parents)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"両親\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "both parents (りょうしん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"両親\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "両親 (りょうしん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"both parents\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "りょうり (cuisine)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"料理\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "cuisine (りょうり)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"料理\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "料理 (りょうり)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"cuisine\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "りょこう (travel)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"旅行\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "travel (りょこう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"旅行\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "旅行 (りょこう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"travel\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "れい (zero)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"零\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "zero (れい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"零\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "零 (れい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"zero\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "れいぞうこ (refrigerator)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"冷蔵庫\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "refrigerator (れいぞうこ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"冷蔵庫\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "冷蔵庫 (れいぞうこ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"refrigerator\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "record", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"レコード\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "レコード", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"record\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "restaurant", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"レストラン\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "レストラン", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"restaurant\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "れんしゅうする (to practice)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"練習\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to practice (れんしゅうする)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"練習\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "練習 (れんしゅうする)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to practice\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ろうか (corridor)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"廊下\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "corridor (ろうか)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"廊下\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "廊下 (ろうか)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"corridor\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ろく (six)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"六\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "six (ろく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"六\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "六 (ろく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"six\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "business shirt", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ワイシャツ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ワイシャツ", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"business shirt\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "わかい (young)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"若い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "young (わかい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"若い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "若い (わかい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"young\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "わかる (to be understood)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"分かる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to be understood (わかる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"分かる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "分かる (わかる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to be understood\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "わすれる (to forget)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"忘れる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to forget (わすれる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"忘れる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "忘れる (わすれる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to forget\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "わたくし ((humble) I, myself)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"私\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "(humble) I, myself (わたくし)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"私\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "私 (わたくし)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"(humble) I, myself\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "わたし (I, myself)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"私\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "I, myself (わたし)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"私\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "私 (わたし)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"I, myself\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "わたす (to hand over)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"渡す\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to hand over (わたす)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"渡す\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "渡す (わたす)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to hand over\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "わたる (to go across)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"渡る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to go across (わたる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"渡る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "渡る (わたる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to go across\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "わるい (bad)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"悪い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "bad (わるい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"悪い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "悪い (わるい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"bad\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "Used for comparison.", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"より、ほう\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "より、ほう", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"Used for comparison.\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }
    ]
}